Fall in love, get married, have a baby. Not necessarily in that order.
The Back-Up Plan is a comedy, romance film directed by Alan Poul.
When Zoe tires of looking for Mr.
Right, she decides to have a baby on her own.
But on the day she's artificially inseminated, she meets Stan, who seems
to be just who she's been searching for all her life.
Now, Zoe has to figure out how to make her two
life's dreams fit with each other.
Zoe, played by Jennifer Lopez.
Stan, played by Alex O'Loughlin.
Mona, played by Michaela Watkins.
Clive, played by Eric Christian Olsen.
Playground Dad, played by Anthony Anderson.
Daphne, played by Noureen DeWulf.
The Back-up Plan (previously known as Plan B) is a 2010 American romantic comedy film directed by Alan Poul,
starring Jennifer Lopez, Alex O'Loughlin, Eric Christian Olsen, Anthony Anderson and Linda Lavin.
The film follows a woman who aims to be a single mother through planned pregnancy, but
soon falls in love with a man who wants to father her unborn children.
It was released theatrically in the United States
on April 23, 2010, by CBS Films.
The Back-up Plan garnered negative reviews from critics, who praised
Lopez's performance but criticized the generic script.
It was a box-office success, grossing $77.5 million
against a production budget of $35 million.
This is Tom Bosley's last film before his death
nearly six months after its release.
The film explores themes of pregnancy, kiss, romcom, sperm bank, doctor.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.